I wake up with blood-shot eyes
我睁开我喷血的眼睛醒过来
Struggled to memorize
拼命去记忆
The way it felt between your thighs
那被你的一切包围的感觉
Pleasure that made you cry
还有那些高兴得令我想哭的事情
Feels so good to be bad
变坏的感觉真好
Not worth the aftermath, after that
不用管结果，在那之后
After that, try to get you back
在那之后，我就要努力把你抢回来
I still don't have the reason
我仍然还没有什么理由
And you don't have the time
而你还没时间
And it really makes me wonder
所以这真的让我想知道
If I ever gave a fuck about you
我到底有没有和你做过（做什么你知道）
Give me something to believe in
给我一些东西去相信
'Cause I don't believe in you anymore, anymore
因为我觉得我不再相信你了
I wonder if it even makes a difference to try, yeah
我想知道你是否做了些什么去改变这一切
So this is goodbye
而这就是离别
God damn I'm standing here
他妈的我站在这里
Decisions that made my bed
决定去整整我的床
Now I must lay in it
我现在必须去整理它了
And deal with things I left unsaid
要处理那些我没说的东西……
I want to dive into you
我想跳到你那儿去
Forget what you're going through
忘记你所经历过的那些事
I get behind, make your move
我在后面，让你动起来
Forget the truth
忘记事实
I still don't have the reason
我仍然还没有什么理由
And you don't have the time
而你还没时间
And it really makes me wonder
所以这真的让我想知道
If I ever gave a fuck about you
我到底有没有和你做过（做什么你知道）
Give me something to believe in
给我一些东西去相信
'Cause I don't believe in you anymore, anymore
因为我觉得我不再相信你了
I wonder if it even makes a difference to try, yeah
我想知道你是否做了些什么去改变这一切
Give me something to believe in
给我一些东西去相信
'Cause I don't believe in you anymore, anymore
因为我觉得我不再相信你了
I wonder if it even makes a difference to try, yeah
我想知道你是否做了些什么去改变这一切
So this is goodbye  waiting me
而这就是离别  跟着我
I've been here before
我来过这里
One day a week
每周来一次
And it won't hurt anymore
而这已经不会让我感到难过了
You caught me in a lie
你识破了我的谎言
I got no alibi
我没什么借口
Why you said you had a meeting
你却以会议为借口
I still don't have the reason
我仍然还没有什么理由
And you don't have the time
而你还没时间
And it really makes me wonder
所以这真的让我想知道
If I ever gave a fuck about you
我到底有没有和你做过（做什么你知道）
So this is goodbye
而这就是离别
非常感谢大家！